hamidashita kaze wo atsumete mitai na
I want to try and gather the unrestrained winds
nami no saki tsutatte kanata e kaketeku
I'll run toward the horizon alongside the wave crests
kakugo wa kimatteru
I've made my decision
michi wa tookutemo
even if there's a long way to go on that road
egaita mirai e tsudzuiteru
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
toki ga bokura wo sekashite kodou ga supiido agetetta
time rushes us, the heartbeat speeds up
yume no naka de mezametemo onaji hikari wo sagashita
when I woke in the middle of a dream, I kept searching for that same light
kagayaku hoshizora no shita kazoekirenai seiza to kage
under the shining star-lit sky, with countless constellations and shadows
sono saki ni kimi wa nani wo nani wo mitsumete iru darou
there was something beyond that, what were you gazing at?
nani wo mitsumete iru darou
what were you gazing at?
I'm exhausted!
Important solo mission, my butt!
They just didn't have enough manpower
for the castle restoration.
That's not the job of a Shinobi.
I won't hold up if
I don't rest somewhere.
I'll take a bath. Here I go!
Hey...
I'm sounding like an old man.
What?!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Thank you.
Who the heck are you, mister?
I'm a Delivery Ninja!
Please ♥ Mister Postman
23, 24, 25...
26...
No mistake...
Thanks to you, Mister Naruto,
all of the postal articles are safe.
By the way, what's a Delivery Ninja?
We are postal professionals
who risk our lives
to deliver the important parcels
our customers have left with us.
In other words, you're a postman.
I am a Delivery Ninja!
Ordinary postmen don't risk their lives.
So you're an awesome postman, huh?
That's right.
Oops, I must not keep
my customers waiting.
Then, I'll be on my way...
Mister! What's your name?!
I'm 596-03.
A zip code...?!
Anywhere would be fine
if I can get in a hot spring...
Cripes...
Here it's still day time and...
That voice...
My, you're a strange one, Jira-Chan.
Am I?
Ah, Pervy Sage!
What?! Who's a Pervy Sage...?!
What's the meaning of this,
Pervy Sage?!
Hadn't you left the village
on an important mission?
That's why I was being patient
about you training with me!
If you've got free time
to be doing this,
help out with my training right now!
Wait, Naruto.
There's a reason for this...
You probably have some glib lies
about gathering information.
You're wrong, you're wrong.
It's data collection, data collection...
You see...
It's my final spurt
for the manuscript of the final volume
of "Make-Out Violence."
What about the mission...?
Well, you see, I'm on a mission.
So, don't worry...
What kind of mission?
As it happens, I received information
that a member of the Akatsuki Organization
will be visiting this town
the day after tomorrow.
The Akatsuki Organization!
Then, that Itachi will be...?
I don't know that.
And the same goes for their purpose...
But that's a matter until
the day after tomorrow.
And so, I'm making effective use
of the free time!
Then it's perfect.
Give me some training!
Well... you see, they're so insistent
about the manuscript.
I ended up promising the publisher
that I'd send it today or tomorrow.
Come on! It's a long-awaited chance
for training.
If my manuscript were
to be completed early,
I might be able to take
some time for training.
Oh, my shoulders are stiff!
There, there.
Oh, I'm thirsty!
Here you go.
Hot!
Hey, the ideas I just about had
have blown away!
Enough!
I'm taking a bath!
What a hard Sensei to please...
I bet he's going to say
this is data collection, anyway.
We must deliver that secret document
to the Land of Fangs,
no matter what the cost...
It seems this is where
the Delivery Ninja always stay.
Oh, they could...
Delivery Ninja?
I can see them now.
This is all I need for
my writing desire to well up...
I'm not getting... inspired with this...
Imagining with your head
is a writer's job, isn't it?
I'm a writer rooted in realism!
Getting a picture is important.
So, I wonder if you'd do that for me.
Can you write if I do that?
I'll write, I'll write!
Sexy Jutsu:
Steam Bath Harem Version!
— Master Jiraiya. Jiraiya!
— This is great!
Won-der-ful!
What a hopeless guy!
He hasn't been able to write at all!
Address, check!
Zip code, check...!
Oh, the sealed documents...
Please take extra care with this.
I will take it for you.
Excuse me, can I also ask you
to take this for me?
Mister Naruto.
Thank you for helping me out yesterday.
Mister!
I am 596-03.
It's hard to remember!
More importantly, I want to ask you
to take care of this!
This goes in a different direction...
Have a heart. Please.
Oh, perfect timing.
Is this a Shadow Clone?
He is 463-72.
This area should be in your jurisdiction.
It is.
Then I leave it to you...
What was it again?
I am 463-72.
Hurry, okay?
Wake up...
I fell asleep!
Pervy Sage, let's start training!
What're you talking about?
I must complete the manuscript...
You don't need to worry
about that.
I wrote the manuscript
and sent it to the publisher!
So, now you can devote
yourself freely to training...
Right, Pervy Sage?
You idiot!
If something like this were read,
it'll be the end of my writing career!
I'm sorry.
You said you sent it to
the publisher, right? How?
I gave it to a Delivery Ninja
in the inn...
Delivery Ninja.
You mean, the one that delivers any
parcel to the addressee, no matter what...
not influenced by any land or
institution... that iron organization?!
After him, Naruto.
We'll chase down the Delivery Ninja,
no matter what...
and retrieve your manuscript
at any cost!
If he's going to the publisher,
he should definitely take this path.
Now what's left is how to
close the time gap...
I hear the leg power of Delivery Ninja
is extraordinary, though...
Pervy Sage!
Slow down the pace a little, man.
Naruto! This is also training!
To be straight, you're short on leg power!
A Ninja must apply oneself,
connecting this with training,
no matter what the situation!
Excellent, Pervy Sage.
Now you're talking!
It's just like a maze!
We're totally lost...
If we had Hinata's or Neji's Byakugan
at a time like this...
Byakugan! I didn't think of that!
That's the Rasengan, isn't it?!
I'm sorry!
Uh, no, you see...!
This isn't the time to be drooling!
There he is!
After him, Naruto.
Right!
Thieves!
Hey, wait!
There's no fool who'd wait
after being told to wait!
As it happens,
the parcel this person here
left with you this morning is a slip-up!
That's right!
I have no knowledge of that.
The rule for us Delivery Ninja
is to deliver parcels to the destination,
even if we have to risk our lives!
My life as a writer is also at risk!
Don't look at me.
This is trouble!
Sorry.
To do that to someone
who's doing honest work...
Shut up! When you get right down to it,
it was you who...
What's this?!
This isn't the thing you wrote!
That time! It got switched with
my manuscript!
Say what?!
This is... a secret document directed
to the feudal lord of the Land of Fangs
from the Land of Claws...
Let me see...
According to the information I've gotten,
the Fang and the Claw could go
to war at any moment...
This is a secret document for peace!
They've decided on peace?!
It's written here.
That's a good thing, isn't it?!
War is no good!
You! You idiot! The fact that
this secret document is here means
the manuscript you wrote is being taken
to the Land of Fangs!
What'll happen if they read it as
a secret document
from the Land of Claws?
This is bad! No doubt, war will begin!
We're going to the Land of Fangs!
Right!
This time for sure we'll take back
the manuscript!
Postal thieves...
my customer's important parcel...!
This is bad!
This is 463-72. This is 463-72!
A postal robbery has occurred!
The thieves are a pair,
a large man with a perverted look
and a kid!
They appear to be after 596-03's parcel.
Members in the area are assigned
to protect 596-03!
Stop the thieves in the name
of the Delivery Ninja!
The only way to get to the Land of Fangs
is to go up this river.
More than likely they will also go
by boat.
Then depending on our speed,
there's a chance we'll catch up.
I'm the one who's got it rough.
You don't have enough physical strength!
Consider this also as training
and apply yourself!
That again?!
Who're those guys?!
It appears reinforcements
have been summoned.
Hurry, Naruto!
Naruto! Switch places!
Rasengan!
Somehow... the Rasengan looks like
a really cheap Jutsu...
It's for the sake of preventing a war!
Our mission of peace is at stake!
— Right!
— Switch.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Rasengan!
That's it!
Hey, wait! It's a slip-up!
This is the real one!
They got switched during the commission!
Delivery Ninja old man,
it's the truth!
I'm sorry.
According to our rule,
we are never to look inside
a customer's parcel we have taken on,
no matter what.
If that passes over to the Land of Fangs,
there will be war!
Even if that were the case,
I must not break the rule.
You're impossible!
It's the Land of Fangs!
All we do is carry out our duties!
Then... we'll take it away
by force if we have to.
— Postal delivery!
Naruto! Do you know which one it is?!
No, I don't!
I am 596-03.
I know! It's 596-03!
Where is he?!
Up there!
Naruto, you hold back the front!
I'll rout the rest!
Got it!
I won't let you go past here!
In the name of the Delivery Ninja,
I will not let anyone interfere!
You're an impressive old man...
I, too, in the name of the Leaf Ninja,
will take away the manuscript
with a Jutsu!
Let's go!
Harem Jutsu! Riverside Mad Dance!
Mis-ter De-Li-very Nin-ja.
No, no! This isn't the time to be
doing something like this.
Now, to get cracking with my delivery.
Deliver...
I will deliver.
Hey, where are you going?
Play with me.
No, no! Not that way.
I'll do my best!
Guys! Give me a hand!
— Right! Yeah.
— Okay!
Postal delivery.
Okay, good work.
This guy's iron will is the real deal...
We're too late, huh...?
Is war going to start?!
This is...!
It's a manuscript of the latest issue
of the Make-Out series!
That Land of Claws feudal lord...!
To think he'd know I was a big fan
of the Make-Out series!
Everyone!
Stop the fighting!
Send a messenger
to the Land of Claws!
Don't let anybody in...
I kind of don't really get it, but...
with this, there'll be no war?
No war is fine...
But does this mean my writing power
is the same as Naruto's scribbling...?!
Now then!
Today's the day the Akatsuki Organization
guy comes!
We'll capture him no matter what
and get information about Sasuke...
Pervy Sage?
Sorry, Naruto. There was a development
while you were sleeping.
I will pursue
the Akatsuki Organization as is.
I've been had!
Well... I suppose it made for
some good training...
kaze ga fuite aa
the wind blows
itai kienai omoi
the pain, the memories won't disappear
nani wo motte ikou ka
what should be brought along?
atsumete hitotsu
assemble them into a piece
nido to nai nido to nai
there is no second chance, never
suteru nante baka mitai
how foolish it is to throw away
mujaki ni natte aa
acting so innocently
imeeji
the images
kitto sore wa owaranai
it probably will not end
ai no mune kogase
burn that love-filled heart
sen no yume watare
sail across a thousand dreams
juuoumujin kakete
running freely
te ni tsukamu sekai
to take hold of the world in hand
kumo ga chigirete
the clouds scatter
hi ga mata ochite
the sun sets yet again
hitori no pareedo ga ugokidasu
the solo parade begins to move
bouken kichijitsu shinpaku joushou
adventure, lucky day, geart beat, rising
meian souguu seimei souai
decisive, encounter, life, mutual love
All right, everyone, follow me.
Wait.
We're heading for
the Village Hidden in Stars
on a mission to protect
a mysterious star.
Naruto!
Man, I'm getting fired up.
We all need to work together here.
Now, let's all unite and show
the boundless power of the Leaf.
Hey, don't be following us like
it's matter of course, Naruto.
You're not listed as
a member for this mission.
Next time:
"Encounter the Boy With the Name of Hoshi."